# **Nathan Sorkin**

#### **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

I'm a full stack developer in NYC with a passion for building great experiences. My focuses are in React, JavaScript / Node, HTML, and CSS/SCSS, but I am always trying to learn new things to expand my skillset and reach my goals of leading a dev team.

www.nathansorkin.com hello@nathansorkin.com (330)-907-9390 Brooklyn, NY

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Full Stack Developer
Locusview
May 2020 - Current

- Working closely with a small tight-knit team to fulfill client feature requests at a rapid pace while still focusing on performance an code clarity
- Implemented new coding practices such as JSDoc, Typescript, ESLint, and Prettier as well as bringing a focus to DRY coding standards.
- Improved runtime of internal applications by 40%

Front End Developer

March 2019 - March 2020

b8ta

- Took initiative to create Node scripts that reduced client and employee workload by converting b8ta's CMS data into easily managed CSV's as well as allowing the user to feed a CSV into the CMS for easy data management and less manual input.
- Communicated directly with clients to discover needs, answer questions surrounding the application and discuss updates as well as our product road map.
- Worked with clients such as Nike, Bonobos, Bluemercury, and others to seamlessly integrate our store locator application into their e-commerce platforms while maintaining the integrity of their style guides.
- Oversaw the agile process as scrum master for each weekly sprint, and helped prioritize work to ensure it aligned with company goals and client road maps.

### **EDUCATION**

# Full Stack Developer Certificate

September 2017 - October 2018

Bloc is a self driven development bootcamp that use projects to build out your knowledge and give you an idea of real world applications. Using a mentor system available to students for help, and support for any questions. Broadening and strengthening my skillset in HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Ruby, Rails, Git, and Node.

## **SKILLS**

- Javascript, HTML, CSS, SCSS, React, Typescript, Node, Git
- Interpersonal Communication, Problem Solving, Project Planning, Time Management
- Figma, Sketch, InDesign, Zeplin